NLRB Briefs, Petitions and other Legal Documents 5318
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Homes Daines Company, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- The Hoover Company (Box 5, Folder 38)
  This document had no date.
- Hoppes Manufacturing Company, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Ann Arbor Press, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Houston and North Texas Motor Freight Lines, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Howell Chevrolet Company, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- The J.L. Hudson Company (Box 5, Folder 43)
  Two cases: One dated 1942, the other 1946
- G.W. Hume Company, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Hughes Tool Company, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Hazel-Atlas Glass Company, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- The Hearst Consolidated Publications, Inc. alongside Newspaper and Mail Deliverers Union of NY and vicinity, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Heiling Bros. Co., 1941 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- H.J. Heinz, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Hekman Furniture Company, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Idaho Potato Growers, Inc., 1944 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Idaho Refining Company, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Illinois Tool Works, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Illinois Bell Telephone Company, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Independent Employees Association at the Neptune Meter Company, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Indiana Metal Products Corporation, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- Indiana Desk Company, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 56b)
- Indiana and Michigan Electric Company, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 57)
- Indianapolis Power & Light Company, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 58)
- Industrial Commissions of the state of Utah, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 58b)
- Industrial Metal Fabrications, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 58c)
- Industrial metal Fabrications, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 59)
- Injection Molding Company, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 59)
- Inland Empire District Council, Lumber and Saw Mill Workers Union, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 60)
- Inland Lime and Stone Company, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 61)
- Inland Steel Company, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 62)
- Iowa Manufacturing Company, a Corporation, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 63)
- W.A. Jones Foundry & Machine Co., a Corporation, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 64)
- Jones Furniture Manufacturing Co, Inc., 1952 (Box 5, Folder 65)
- Jones & Laughlin Steel Corporation (Box 5, Folder 66)
  Several cases: No.s 9730, 9334, 418-419, 9317
- Jos. N. Fourier, Rome Lincoln-Mercury Group, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 67)
- Sidran Sportswear, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 68)
- Joseph J. Michalik d/b/a Service Metal Industries, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 69)
- Joy Silk Mills, Inc., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 70)
- Kentucky Utilities Company, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 71)
  Two cases: one in 1951, the other in 1949
- Keystone Steel & Wire Company, Independent Steel Workers Alliance, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 72)
- Keystone Freight Lines, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 73)
- W.T. Killebrew, et al, d/b/a Hopkinsville Clothing Manufacturing Company, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 74)
- Kingston Cake Company, Inc. Kingston Mutual Association, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 75)
- Kirmer Motors, Inc, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 76)
- Knickerbocker Plastic Co., 1952 (Box 5, Folder 77)
- Kopman-Woracek Shoe Mfg. Co., 1946 (Box 5, Folder 78)
- S.G. Kress & Company, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 79)
- Ken Rose Motors, Inc., 1951 (Box 5, Folder 80)
- Kennametal, Inc., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 81)
- Louisville Refining Company, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Loveman, Joseph & Loeb, a corporation, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- R.J. Louvvorn, d/b/a Georgia Twine & Cordage Co., 1948 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- George Whitaker, A.M. Debruhl, T.G. Embler, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- The Lummus Company, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- The Locomotive Finished Material Company, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Longview Furniture Company, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- P. Lorillard Company, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Los Angeles Brick & Clay Products, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Los Angeles Building and Construction Trades Council, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Local 1250, Retail, Wholesale Department Store Union of America (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Local 1796, United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Local 2880, Lumber & Sawmill Workers Union, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Local Union 12, Progressive Mine Workers of America, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Local 743, United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Local 1031, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Local Union No. 1229, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- W.E. Lipshutz, d/b/a The Monarch Company, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Litchfield Manufacturing Company, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Laister-Kauffmann Aircraft Co (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Laister-Kauffmann Aircraft Corporation, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Lakey Foundry and Machine Company, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Lake Superior Lumber Corporation, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Landis Tool Company, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Lane Cotton Mill Company, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- La Salle Steel Company, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Lebanon Steel Foundry (Box 6, Folder 26)
  No. 7990, no date available.
- Lehigh Portland Cement company, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Lettie Lee, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Le Tourneau Company of Georgia, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Lewis & Holmes Motor Freight Company, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- J.C. Lewis Motor Company, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Lightner Publishing Corporation of Illinois, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Moss Planing Mill Company, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Motorola, Inc., 1952 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Motor Valve & Manufacturing Company, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Mt. Clemens Pottery Company, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Mueller Brass Co., 1949 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Mylan-Sparta company, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Monumental Life Insurance Company, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Mooresville Mills, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Mooresville Cotton Mills, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Morand Brothers Beverage (Box 6, Folder 42)
  Two files: 10727 (date 1953), 10355 (no date)
- Morrison Turning Co., 1949 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Montgomery Ward & Co. (Box 6, Folder 44)
  Two cases: 6826 (1939), 10108 (1942)
- Midland Steel Products Company, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Milan Shirt Manufacturing Company, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Minnesota Mining & Manufacturing Company, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Mississippi Products, Inc. (Box 6, Folder 48)
  No date. NO. 14753
- Model Mill Company, Inc., 1953 (Box 6, Folder 49)
- Monarch Machine Tool Company, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 50)
- Mid-Continent Petroleum Corporation, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Mid-Co Gasoline Company, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 52)
- Joseph J Michalik, d/b/a Service Metal Industries, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 53)
- Metal Moldings Corporation, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 54)
- Metallic Building Corporation, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 55)
- Mexia Textile Mills, Inc., 1949 (Box 6, Folder 56)
- Machine Products Company, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 57)
- Mackay Radio & Telegraph Co., 1935 (Box 6, Folder 58)
- Magee Carpet Company, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 59)
- R.C. Mahon Company, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 60)
- L.L. Majure Transportation Company, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 61)
- Mall Tool Company, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 62)
- Marshall Field & Company, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 63)
- Lewis Meier & Co., 1947 (Box 6, Folder 64)
- Massey Gin & Machine Works, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 65)
- Mathieson Alkali Works Inc., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 66)
- Mavis Lane, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 67)
- Famous Barr Company, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 68)
- McGough Bakeries Corporation, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 69)
- Service Parts Company, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 70)
- Memphis Furniture Manufacturing Company, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 71)
- Marshall Field & Company, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 72)
- Martel Mills Company, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 73)
- Local 57, Intl. Union of Operating Engineers, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 74)
- Local 74, United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 75)
- Local 404, Intl. Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 76)
- Leland-Gifford Company (Box 6, Folder 77)
  Two cases: 4654 (in 1952) and 3926 (in 1943)
- C.D. Beck & Company, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 78)
- Haleston Drug Stores, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Hallan & Boggs Truck & Implement Co., 1952 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- M.A. Hanna Company, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Happ Brothers Company, Inc., 1952 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Harbison-Walker Refractories Company, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Harding College, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Harris-Woodson Co., Inc., 1947 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Harrison Sheet Steel Company, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Top Mode Manufacturing Co., 1952 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Hart Cotton Mills, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Hartsell Mils Company, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Hawk & Buck Company, Inc., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Lion Brand Manufacturing Company, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union, Local 10 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  Three cases: 12907 (1952), 13183 (1952), and 13851 (no date)
- International Rice Milling Company, Inc., 1950 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- International Union of Operating Engineers, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Local 57, International Union of Operating Engineers and John A. White, Sr., 1952 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- International Union of United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (Box 7, Folder 18)
  Two cases: 1949 and 1951
- Neptune Meter Company, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- United Automobile Workers of America, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- United Automobile Workers of A (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Irving Air Chute Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Sue-Ann Manufacturing Company, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Itasca Cotton Manufacturing Company, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- International Association of Machinist, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- International Furniture Company, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Jack Smith Beverages, Inc., 1952 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Jackson Packing Company and John H. Bowman, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Surprise Candy Company, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- The Jacobs Manufacturing Company, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- James Thompson & Co, Inc., 1953 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Jamestown Veneer and Plywood Corporation, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Jarka Corporation of Philadelphia, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Jefferson Electric Company, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Jefferson Electric C (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Inter-city advertising Company of Greensboro, NC & Inter-city advertising Company of Charlottesville, NC, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Interlake Iron Corporation (Box 7, Folder 37)
  No date. NO. 7905
- International Union, United Mine Workers of America, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Iowa Manufacturing Company, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Joanna Cotton Mills Company, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- John H. Barr Marketing Co., 1953 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- John S. Barnes Corporation, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- John W. Campbell, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Johnson Bronze Company, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- C.D. Johnson Lumber Corporation and Willamette Valley Lumber Operators Association, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Joliet Cash and Carry Lumber Company, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Harold Hamilton (Box 7, Folder 47)
  No date. NO. 10247
- The Kansas Milling Co. (Box 7, Folder 48)
  No date. NO. 4036
- Katz Drug Company, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 49)
- Lee's Department Store (Box 7, Folder 50)
  No date. NO. 12827
- Kearney & Trecker Corporation, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 51)
- Kellburn Manufacturing Company, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 52)
- Kelco Corporation, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 53)
- Kuehne Manufacturing Company, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 54)
- Kropp F (Box 7, Folder 55)
- Kropp Forge Company & Kropp Forge Aviation Co., 1949 (Box 7, Folder 55)
- E.W. Saybolt & Company, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 56)
- Capolino Packing Corporation, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 57)
- Scullin Steel Company, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 58)
- Seamprufe, Incorporated, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 59)
- Security Warehouse and Cold Storage Company (Box 7, Folder 60)
  No date. NO. 10182
- Stonewall Cotton Mills, Inc., 1942 (Box 7, Folder 61)
- Stowe Spinning Company (Box 7, Folder 62)
  NO. 46 (1948), NO. 5640 (1947)
- Startford Furniture Corporation, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 63)
- R.W. Sturges, Sr. d/b/a The Sturges Company, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 64)
- Sunshine Mining Company, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 65)
- Super-Cold Southwest Company, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 66)
- Superior Company ,Inc., 1952 (Box 7, Folder 67)
- Superior Engineering Company, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 68)
- Russell Kingston, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 69)
- Russell Manufacturing Co., 1950 (Box 7, Folder 70)
- Salant & Salant, Inc. (Box 7, Folder 71)
  Two cases: NO. 10672 (1948), NO. 10445 (1950)
- Salmon and Cowin Inc., Mining Engineers & Contractors (Box 7, Folder 72)
  No date. NO 11138
- Salt River Valley Water Users; association, an Arizona corporation, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 73)
- Wallick and Schwalm Company, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 74)
- Sam Zall Milling, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 75)
- Star Beef Company, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 76)
- San Diego Gas and Electric Company, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- The Sandy Hill Iron & Brass Works, a Corporation, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Sanson Hosiery Mills, Inc., 1951 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- C.E. Sawyer, d/b/a Sawyer Industrial Sheet Metal Fabricators, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Saxe-Glassman Shoe Corporation, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Quincy Steel Casting Company, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Quest-Shon Mark Brassiere Co. Inc., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- R.B. Guerin & Company, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Robbins Tire and Rubber Company, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Rock Hil Printing and Finishing Company (Box 8, Folder 10)
  Two cases: 4904 and 4944
- Rockaway News Supply Co., Inc., 1952 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Roebling Employees Association & John A. Roebling Son's Company (Box 8, Folder 12)
  Two cases, both dated 1940. Case #: 7263
- Rogue Valley Broadcasting Co., Inc., 1952 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- W.W. Rosenbraugh Company, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Ross Gear and Tool Company, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Roure-Dupont Manufacturing, Inc., 1952 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Roxboro Cotton Mills, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Royal Palm Ice Company, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Rozelle Shoe Corporation, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Penokee Veneer Company and Splicewood Corporation, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Peoples Motor Express, Inc. (Box 8, Folder 21)
  No date. Case#: 5687
- Pequanoc Rubber Company, Soft Rubber Workers, Inc., 1942 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Perfect Circle Company, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Perfection Steel Body Company, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- M.E. Greenfield Company, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Peyton Packing Co. (Box 8, Folder 26)
  No date. Case #: 10960
- Phillips Petroleum Company, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- The Phoenix Mutual Life Insurance Company, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Piedmont Cotton Mills, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Piedmont Wagon & Manufacturing Company, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Pacific Mills, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Packard Motor car Company, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  Two cases: 658, 10157
- Pappas and Company and Fresh Fruit and Vegetables Workers Union, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Parker Brothers and Company, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Parkers Prairie Cooperative Creamery Association, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- United Telephone Organizations, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Paul M. Herzog, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Prigg Boat Works, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Pecheur Lozenge Co., 1953 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Peerless Quarries, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Peninsular & Occidental Steamship Company, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Pennsylvania Greyhound Lines, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Pennwoven, Inc., 1951 (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Pacific-Gamble Robinson Co., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Pacific Gas & El (Box 8, Folder 45)
- Pacific Electric & Gas Company, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 45)
- Pacific Greyhound Lines, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 46)
- Pierce Brothers, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 47)
- Piqua Munising (Box 8, Folder 48)
- Piqua Munising Wood Products Company, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 48)
- Pinkerton's National Detective Agency, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 49)
- W (Box 8, Folder 50)
- Pittsburgh Steamship Company, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 50)
- Plankinton Packing Company, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 51)
- Planters Manufacturing Company, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 52)
- F.W. Poe Manufacturing Company, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 53)
- Polish National Alliance of the United States of America, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 54)
- Polson Logging Company, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 55)
- Polynesian Arts, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 56)
- Pool Manufacturing Company, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 57)
- Poole Foundry and Machine Company, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 58)
- Porcelain Steels, Inc., 1943 (Box 8, Folder 59)
- Port Gibson Veneer & Box Company, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 60)
- Postex Cotton Mills, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 61)
- Potlach Forests, Inc., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 62)
- Pratt, Read & Company, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 63)
- Printing Specialties and Paper Converters Union, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 64)
- Precision Fabricators (Box 8, Folder 65)
  No date. No case number. NO NOTHING (except a reply brief).
- Prudential Insurance Company of America, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 66)
- Public Service Coordinated Transport, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 67)
- Pure Oil Company and Oil Workers International Union (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Quality and Service Laundry, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Quarles Manufacturing Company and Southern Wholesalers, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Queen City Valves, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Radio Officers Union of the Commercial Telegraphs Union, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Rathbyn Molding Corporation (Box 9, Folder 6)
- The W.T. Raleigh Company, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Ray Brooks, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Ray Smith Transport Company, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Red Arrow Freight Lines, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Red Arrow Freight Lines, Brown Express, Johnson Motor Lines, Red Ball Motor Freight Lines, Sproles Motor Freight Lines, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Red Star Express Lines of Auburn, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Reed & Prince Manufacturing Company, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Reeder Motor Company, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Reeves Rubber, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Register Publishing, Co., 1943 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Register Publishing (Box 9, Folder 17)
  No date. NO. 10364
- Republic Aviation Corporation, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Republican Publishing Company, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Revolution Flannel Workers Union, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Reynolds Corporation, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Reynolds International Pen Company, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Richter's Bakery, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- The Ridge Tool Company, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Riverside Manufacturing Company, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- The Rivoli Mills, Inc., 1953 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Standard Dry Wall Products, Inc. (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Standard Dry Wall Products, Inc., 1951 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Standard Lime and Stone Company, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Standard Oil Company, Sohio Pipe Line Corporation, Latonia Refining Corporation, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Standard Oil Company, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Standard Steel Spring Company, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Standard Trouser Company, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- State Center Warehouse and Cold Storage Company, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- State of Florida ex. Rel. J. Tom Watson (Attorney General), 1945 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  Brief for Appellee
- Sterling Furniture Company, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Stewart-Warner Corporation, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- W.E. Stewart and Lela Stewart, d/b/a Stewart Oil Co., 1953 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- The Stilley Plywood Company, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Stocker Manufacturing Company, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Stokely Foods, Inc., 1951 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Stonewall Cotton Mills, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Sement-Solvay Company, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- Semi-Steel Casting Company, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Servel, Inc., 1945 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- Service Trade Chauffeurs, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 45)
- Seven-Up Bottling Company, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 46)
- Sewell Hats (Box 9, Folder 47)
- Sewell Manufacturing Company, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 48)
- Sharples Chemicals, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 49)
- Shawnee Milking Company, d/b/a Paul's Valley Milking Company, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 49b)
- Shell Oil Company, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 50)
- Shen-Valley Meat Packers, Inc., 1953 (Box 9, Folder 51)
- Simmons Company, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 52)
- A-1 Photo Service, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 53)
- Smith Transfer Company, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 54)
- Oberman & Company, 1937 (Box 9, Folder 55)
- Odanah Iron Company, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 56)
- Odenbach Shipbuilding Company, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 57)
- Oertel Brewing Company, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 58)
- Office Towel Supply Company, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 59)
- Ohio Calcium Company, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 60)
- Ohio Ferro-Alloys Corporation (Box 9, Folder 61)
- Ohio Fuel Gas Company, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 62)
- Ohio Power Company, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 63)
- Ohio Public Service Company, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 64)
- Nebel Knitting Company, Inc., 1939 (Box 9, Folder 65)
- C. Nelson Manufacturing Company, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 66)
- Independent Employees Association of the Neptune Meter Company, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 67)
- Ohio Associated Telephone Company, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 68)
- Ozark Dam Constructors and Flippin Materials, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 69)
- Ozark Harwood Company, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 70)
- Owens-Illinois Glass Company (Box 9, Folder 71)
  Two cases: 1941 (8707) and 1949 (9785)
- Oregon Worsted Company, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 72)
- Oklahoma Transportation Company, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 73)
- Olin Industries, Winchester Repeating Arms Company Division, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 74)
- Pioneer Electric Company, United Steelworkers of America, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 75)
- Ohio Public Service Company, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 76)
- Louis K. Nathanielson, trustee in bankruptcy of MacKenzie Coach Lines, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 77)
- Nu Car Carriers, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 78)
- W.C. Nabors, d/b/a Nabors Company, Inc., 1951 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- United Department Store Workers of New York, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- National Biscuit Company, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- National Broadcasting Company, Inc. American Broadcasting Company, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- National Die Casting Company, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- National Garment Company, and Wells-Wear Company, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- National Gar (Box 10, Folder 6)
- National Garment Company, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- National Maritime Union of America, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- National Motor Bearing Company (Box 10, Folder 9)
  No date. Case NO. 8869
- The National Plastics Product Company, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- National Tool Company, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Martin Brothers Box Company, 1942 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Maryland Drydock Company, 1950 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Mason Manufacturing Company, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Massey Gin and Machine Works, Inc., 1949 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Marshall Field & Company, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Marshall Field & Company, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Metal Moldings Corporation, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' Union of New York and Vicinity, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- D.W. Newton, d/b/a Newton Brothers Lumber Company, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Niles Fire Brick Company, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Niles-Cement-Pond Company, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Norfolk Shipbuilding and Drydock, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Norfolk Southern Bus Corporation, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Norma Mining Corporation, Alfredton Coal Company, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Norris Incorporated, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- North Electric Manufacturing Company, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- North (Box 10, Folder 26)
- North Whittier Heights Citrus Association, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Northwestern Mutual Fire Association, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Nina Dye Works Co, Inc., 1952 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- New Idea, Inc. and New Idea Shop Association, Inc. (Box 10, Folder 29)
  No date. Case NO. 9134